{
    "subject": "resource/Nusrat_Fateh_Ali_Khan",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1948-10-13",
    "human_readable": "Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan was born on 1948-10-13.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9340250492095947,
            "question": "When was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9326061010360718,
            "question": "On which date was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8605948686599731,
            "question": "What year marks the birth of Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8211039304733276,
            "question": "Is Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's birthdate October 13th?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.815167248249054,
            "question": "What is the full birthdate of Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7988853454589844,
            "question": "Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's birthdate is October 13th, what year did he enter the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7805097103118896,
            "question": "In what month was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6874154806137085,
            "question": "What day of the month was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5626538991928101,
            "question": "What is the month and day of Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5049407482147217,
            "question": "If someone were to celebrate Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's birthday, what date would they use?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan was born on 1948-10-13.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1975_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the month and day of Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1975_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What day of the month was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1975_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what month was Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1975_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1975_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents consistently provide the birth date of Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan as October 13, 1948. Therefore, the statement \"Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan was born on 1948-10-13\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}